{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1409","name":"Manna Meals","address":"1950 Trumbull","zipcode":"48216","owner":"MANNA COMM MEAL BOARD OF DIR","licenseNumber":"035569","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/27/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000F4EBF0053DC454C0882F3D7B5D2A4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43439","establishmentid":"1409","name":"Manna Meals","inspectionDate":"2018-09-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"130","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43439","inspectionDate":"9/18/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1409","name":"Manna Meals","violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\r\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\r\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\r\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\r\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\r\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\r\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\r\n\r\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Chlorine solution concentration","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 25 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"SANITIZER BUCKETS","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-09-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above."}]},{"inspectionid":"41538","establishmentid":"1409","name":"Manna Meals","inspectionDate":"2018-02-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"79","pcount":"4","pfcount":"2","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"6","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"6","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41538","inspectionDate":"2/20/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1409","name":"Manna Meals","violationCode":"4-703.11","violationDescription":"After being cleaned, EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be SANITIZED  by an approved process.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Chlorine solution","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not immersed in","subProblem":"","location":"THREE COMPARTMENT SINK","subLocation":"In the Third Compartment","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Completely submerse equipment/utensil."},{"inspectionid":"41538","inspectionDate":"2/20/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1409","name":"Manna Meals","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"SERVING LINE","subLocation":"In the Bus bin","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"41538","inspectionDate":"2/20/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1409","name":"Manna Meals","violationCode":"5-202.13","violationDescription":"An air gap between the water supply inlet and the flood level rim of the PLUMBING FIXTURE, EQUIPMENT, or nonFOOD EQUIPMENT shall be at least twice the diameter of the water supply inlet and may not be less than 1 inch. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Air gap","subItem":"between drain line and flood rim of receiving drain","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the Drain line","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"inspectionid":"41538","inspectionDate":"2/20/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1409","name":"Manna Meals","violationCode":"4-502.11","violationDescription":"(A) UTENSILS shall be maintained in a state of repair or condition that complies with the requirements specified under Parts 4-1 and 4-2 or shall be discarded.\r\n(B) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be calibrated in accordance with manufacturer's specifications as necessary to ensure their accuracy. (Pf)   \r\n(C) Ambient air temperature, water pressure, and water TEMPERATURE MEAURING DEVICES shall be maintained in good repair and be accurate within the intended range of use.","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"probe","problemDescription":"Not calibrated","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Calibrate in accordance with manufacturer specifications."},{"inspectionid":"41538","inspectionDate":"2/20/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1409","name":"Manna Meals","violationCode":"4-501.116","violationDescription":"Concentration of the SANITIZING solution shall be accurately determined by using a test kit or other device. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not used","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"For the Sanitizer","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Use test kit to verify sanitizer concentration."},{"inspectionid":"41538","inspectionDate":"2/20/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1409","name":"Manna Meals","violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not comply with law","subProblem":"","location":"WIPING CLOTHS","subLocation":"In the Wiping cloth bucket","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove and replace to be in compliance with law."}]},{"inspectionid":"39916","establishmentid":"1409","name":"Manna Meals","inspectionDate":"2017-09-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"83","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"39916","inspectionDate":"9/15/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1409","name":"Manna Meals","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not meet requirements of rule","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements of rule."},{"inspectionid":"39916","inspectionDate":"9/15/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1409","name":"Manna Meals","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."}]},{"inspectionid":"37893","establishmentid":"1409","name":"Manna Meals","inspectionDate":"2017-01-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"2","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"37893","inspectionDate":"1/27/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1409","name":"Manna Meals","violationCode":"5-202.13","violationDescription":"An air gap between the water supply inlet and the flood level rim of the PLUMBING FIXTURE, EQUIPMENT, or nonFOOD EQUIPMENT shall be at least twice the diameter of the water supply inlet and may not be less than 1 inch. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Air gap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than twice the diameter of supply line","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-01-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"inspectionid":"37893","inspectionDate":"1/27/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1409","name":"Manna Meals","violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \r\n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \r\n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Equipment/utensils","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-01-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store toxics below and away from all other items."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1409"}}